FiveThirtyEight Politics https://fivethirtyeight.com/podcasts/ en-us 2015 Nate Silver and the FiveThirtyEight team cover the latest in politics, tracking the issues and "game-changers" every week. https://images.megaphone.fm/96ITpFeyoyyiQy2NJ9w-q-ufr8KwygAAlcfQAEwjqzg/plain/s3://megaphone-prod/podcasts/eff766c2-63ae-11ea-9caa-8b87e9a0e007/image/i.png FiveThirtyEight Politics https://fivethirtyeight.com/podcasts/ no episodic Nate Silver and the FiveThirtyEight team cover the latest in politics, tracking the issues and "game-changers" every week. FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Nate Silver and the FiveThirtyEight team cover the latest in politics, tracking the issues and "game-changers" every week.  FiveThirtyEight.com espndigitalaudiocontent@espn.com https://feeds.megaphone.fm/ESP8794877317 It's Not Just The Economy, Stupid After the release of historically bad GDP data, the crew discusses how well economic data can predict the outcome of an election. They also discuss the potential consequences of President Trump casting doubt on the legitimacy of the 2020 election. Mon, 03 Aug 2020 21:56:05 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver After the release of historically bad GDP data, the crew discusses how well economic data can predict the outcome of an election. They also discuss the potential consequences of President Trump casting doubt on the legitimacy of the 2020 election.  3094  A GOP Congressman Who Might Not Vote For Trump Rep. Will Hurd of Texas’s 23rd Congressional District joins the podcast. He is one of only four Republicans in the House still representing a district that Hillary Clinton won in 2016 and he is the only Black Republican in the chamber. He is also retiring at the end of his current term. As he says on the podcast, he is not yet sure whether he will vote for President Trump this fall. Thu, 30 Jul 2020 21:24:22 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Rep. Will Hurd of Texas’s 23rd Congressional District joins the podcast. He is one of only four Republicans in the House still representing a district that Hillary Clinton won in 2016 and he is the only Black Republican in the chamber. He is also retiring at the end of his current term. As he says on the podcast, he is not yet sure whether he will vote for President Trump this fall.  1626  Biden's VP Pick Could Be Days Away According to the timeframe Biden laid out, he could announce his choice for a running mate as soon as the end of this week. The crew discusses the upsides and downsides of his various choices. Mon, 27 Jul 2020 22:22:53 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver According to the timeframe Biden laid out, he could announce his choice for a running mate as soon as the end of this week. The crew discusses the upsides and downsides of his various choices.  4088  The U.S. Still Isn't Prepared For A Pandemic Election In March, it became clear that states needed to reconfigure in-person voting and significantly scale up mail voting so that Americans could vote during a pandemic. Since then, we’ve seen postponed elections, consolidated polling places, long lines, mail ballots that never reached voters, and long delays in counting those ballots. Will the U.S. be ready in November? Thu, 23 Jul 2020 22:10:59 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In March, it became clear that states needed to reconfigure in-person voting and significantly scale up mail voting so that Americans could vote during a pandemic. Since then, we’ve seen postponed elections, consolidated polling places, long lines, mail ballots that never reached voters, and long delays in counting those ballots. Will the U.S. be ready in November?  2346  There Aren't Secret Trump Voters A recent poll showed that the majority of Pennsylvanians think that people in their community secretly support Trump. The crew explains why that is unlikely. They also consider the future of Black politics as politicians from the Civil Rights Era -- like Rep. John Lewis -- leave office. Mon, 20 Jul 2020 22:41:36 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver A recent poll showed that the majority of Pennsylvanians think that people in their community secretly support Trump. The crew explains why that is unlikely. They also consider the future of Black politics as politicians from the Civil Rights Era -- like Rep. John Lewis -- leave office.  3384  White Democrats Are Wary Of Big Ideas To Address Racial Inequality In recent weeks, public opinion has moved significantly in favor of Black Lives Matter and more people have taken the view that Black people face discrimination in America. But is there public support for policies that could address that discrimination? FiveThirtyEight's Perry Bacon Jr. and political science professor Meredith Conroy discuss what the polls can tell us. Thu, 16 Jul 2020 23:54:20 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In recent weeks, public opinion has moved significantly in favor of Black Lives Matter and more people have taken the view that Black people face discrimination in America. But is there public support for policies that could address that discrimination? FiveThirtyEight's Perry Bacon Jr. and political science professor Meredith Conroy discuss what the polls can tell us.  2956  COVID-19 Deaths Are Rising. What Will The U.S. Do? The crew discusses whether Americans and politicians are in agreement on how to respond to the recent surge in coronavirus cases. The also interrogate a lesson that some Democrats took away from the 2016 election -- that the party should focus less on "identity politics." Mon, 13 Jul 2020 22:41:00 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses whether Americans and politicians are in agreement on how to respond to the recent surge in coronavirus cases. The also interrogate a lesson that some Democrats took away from the 2016 election -- that the party should focus less on "identity politics."  3269  Conservatives Didn’t Get The SCOTUS They Wanted This Term FiveThirtyEight legal reporter Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins Galen Druke to look back at a U.S. Supreme Court term full of consequential cases. They also unpack one the final rulings of the term, which permits prosecutors to subpoena the president's financial records. Thu, 09 Jul 2020 21:15:43 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver FiveThirtyEight legal reporter Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins Galen Druke to look back at a U.S. Supreme Court term full of consequential cases. They also unpack one the final rulings of the term, which permits prosecutors to subpoena the president's financial records.  1957  How Trump Could Improve His Electoral Odds The crew considers various strategies that President Trump and Republicans could use to improve their electoral prospects this fall -- ranging from a new running mate to a vacancy on the U.S. Supreme Court. Mon, 06 Jul 2020 22:53:30 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew considers various strategies that President Trump and Republicans could use to improve their electoral prospects this fall -- ranging from a new running mate to a vacancy on the U.S. Supreme Court.  3385  How The GOP Chose To Be A White Party FiveThirtyEight's Clare Malone discusses the history of how the GOP became an overwhelmingly white party. Her article on the topic is titled, "The Republican Choice: How a party spent decades making itself white." Thu, 02 Jul 2020 19:43:48 -0000 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver FiveThirtyEight's Clare Malone discusses the history of how the GOP became an overwhelmingly white party. Her article on the topic is titled, "The Republican Choice: How a party spent decades making itself white."  2465  Biden Is Currently Competitive In Georgia And Texas The crew looks at new polling that shows the clearest picture so far of the presidential race in battleground states. It isn't good for Trump. Mon, 29 Jun 2020 22:18:00 -0000 Biden Is Currently Competitive In Georgia And Texas full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew looks at new polling that shows the clearest picture so far of the presidential race in battleground states. It isn't good for Trump. The crew looks at new polling that shows the clearest picture so far of the presidential race in battleground states. It isn't good for Trump.  2741 no  New Voter Registrations Have Nosedived During COVID-19 FiveThirtyEight's Nathaniel Rakich and Kaleigh Rogers analyze data showing that the number of people registering to vote has fallen off a cliff during the coronavirus pandemic Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:39:00 -0000 New Voter Registrations Have Nosedived During COVID-19 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver FiveThirtyEight's Nathaniel Rakich and Kaleigh Rogers analyze data showing that the number of people registering to vote has fallen off a cliff during the coronavirus pandemic FiveThirtyEight's Nathaniel Rakich and Kaleigh Rogers analyze data showing that the number of people registering to vote has fallen off a cliff during the coronavirus pandemic  1979 no  Progressives Challenge The Democratic Establishment The crew looks at the dynamic between Democratic upstarts and the establishment as primary voters head to the polls in New York and Kentucky. Mon, 22 Jun 2020 21:34:00 -0000 Progressives Challenge The Democratic Establishment full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew looks at the dynamic between Democratic upstarts and the establishment as primary voters head to the polls in New York and Kentucky. The crew looks at the dynamic between Democratic upstarts and the establishment as primary voters head to the polls in New York and Kentucky.  2897 no  Model Talk: Biden Leads Trump By 9 Nationally In this edition of Model Talk, Nate and Galen discuss FiveThirtyEight's newly published presidential election polling averages. Thu, 18 Jun 2020 23:17:00 -0000 Model Talk: Biden Leads Trump By 9 Nationally full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In this edition of Model Talk, Nate and Galen discuss FiveThirtyEight's newly published presidential election polling averages. In this edition of Model Talk, Nate and Galen discuss FiveThirtyEight's newly published presidential election polling averages.  2461 no  Views Of BLM Have Shifted. What Happens Next? The crew discusses the ways that public opinion on racism has changed during the past three weeks and ask how it will affect our politics. Mon, 15 Jun 2020 22:05:00 -0000 Views Of BLM Have Shifted. What Happens Next? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the ways that public opinion on racism has changed during the past three weeks and ask how it will affect our politics. The crew discusses the ways that public opinion on racism has changed during the past three weeks and ask how it will affect our politics.  3189 no  The Protests Appear To Be Working New York Times writer Mara Gay and FiveThirtyEight contributor Shom Mazumder join the podcast to discuss the efficacy of the anti-police violence protests so far. Fri, 12 Jun 2020 16:29:00 -0000 The Protests Appear To Be Working full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver New York Times writer Mara Gay and FiveThirtyEight contributor Shom Mazumder join the podcast to discuss the efficacy of the anti-police violence protests so far. New York Times writer Mara Gay and FiveThirtyEight contributor Shom Mazumder join the podcast to discuss the efficacy of the anti-police violence protests so far.  1547 no  Americans Don't Like How Trump Is Handling Multiple Crises The podcast crew looks at President Trump's latest polling for handling the pandemic and mass protests. They also discuss why young voters aren't enthusiastic about Biden. Mon, 08 Jun 2020 21:51:00 -0000 Americans Don't Like How Trump Is Handling Multiple Crises full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew looks at President Trump's latest polling for handling the pandemic and mass protests. They also discuss why young voters aren't enthusiastic about Biden. The podcast crew looks at President Trump's latest polling for handling the pandemic and mass protests. They also discuss why young voters aren't enthusiastic about Biden.  3309 no  Protests, Then And Now Prof. Yohuru Williams joins Perry Bacon Jr. and Galen Druke to discuss how today's anti-police violence protests compare with past protest movements. Thu, 04 Jun 2020 21:10:00 -0000 Protests, Then And Now full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Prof. Yohuru Williams joins Perry Bacon Jr. and Galen Druke to discuss how today's anti-police violence protests compare with past protest movements. Prof. Yohuru Williams joins Perry Bacon Jr. and Galen Druke to discuss how today's anti-police violence protests compare with past protest movements.  2707 no  The Data Behind Police Violence Sam Sinyangwe joins the podcast to discuss police violence data and the politics of the protests that have spread across the country. Mon, 01 Jun 2020 21:43:00 -0000 The Data Behind Police Violence full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Sam Sinyangwe joins the podcast to discuss police violence data and the politics of the protests that have spread across the country. Sam Sinyangwe joins the podcast to discuss police violence data and the politics of the protests that have spread across the country.  3576 no  What Biden's VP Picks Say About Him Perry Bacon Jr. and Julia Azari join the podcast to discuss the process of choosing a VP and what that choice says about the candidate and the party. Thu, 28 May 2020 22:46:00 -0000 What Biden's VP Picks Say About Him full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Perry Bacon Jr. and Julia Azari join the podcast to discuss the process of choosing a VP and what that choice says about the candidate and the party. Perry Bacon Jr. and Julia Azari join the podcast to discuss the process of choosing a VP and what that choice says about the candidate and the party.  2083 no  Questions About Biden And Trump's Bases The crew discusses a gaffe Biden made during a conversation about black voters and debates the findings of a new study about white working class voters in the 2016 election. Tue, 26 May 2020 22:16:00 -0000 Questions About Biden And Trump's Bases full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses a gaffe Biden made during a conversation about black voters and debates the findings of a new study about white working class voters in the 2016 election. The crew discusses a gaffe Biden made during a conversation about black voters and debates the findings of a new study about white working class voters in the 2016 election.  3702 no  One Virus, A World Full Of Responses The COVID-19 pandemic has shown how many countries, with different political systems, handle a very similar crisis -- and how the public reacts. Thu, 21 May 2020 22:05:00 -0000 One Virus, A World Full Of Responses full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The COVID-19 pandemic has shown how many countries, with different political systems, handle a very similar crisis -- and how the public reacts. The COVID-19 pandemic has shown how many countries, with different political systems, handle a very similar crisis -- and how the public reacts.  2643 no  Does Trump Really Want A Fight With Obama? The crew looks at evidence that the coronavirus response has grown more partisan. They also discuss the rationale for an election year conflict between Obama and Trump. Mon, 18 May 2020 21:52:00 -0000 Does Trump Really Want A Fight With Obama? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew looks at evidence that the coronavirus response has grown more partisan. They also discuss the rationale for an election year conflict between Obama and Trump. The crew looks at evidence that the coronavirus response has grown more partisan. They also discuss the rationale for an election year conflict between Obama and Trump.  3190 no  Why COVID-19 Conspiracy Theories Are Spreading Political scientist Joe Uscinski joins the podcast to discuss the spread of COVID-19 conspiracy theories -- why they've formed and what can be done about them. Thu, 14 May 2020 21:12:00 -0000 Why COVID-19 Conspiracy Theories Are Spreading full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Political scientist Joe Uscinski joins the podcast to discuss the spread of COVID-19 conspiracy theories -- why they've formed and what can be done about them. Political scientist Joe Uscinski joins the podcast to discuss the spread of COVID-19 conspiracy theories -- why they've formed and what can be done about them.  2701 no  Americans, Not Politicians, Will Decide How We Reopen The podcast crew discusses the politics and practicalities of states reopening amid the COVID-19 pandemic. They also consider which party is ahead in the race for the Senate. Mon, 11 May 2020 20:57:00 -0000 Americans, Not Politicians, Will Decide How We Reopen full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew discusses the politics and practicalities of states reopening amid the COVID-19 pandemic. They also consider which party is ahead in the race for the Senate. The podcast crew discusses the politics and practicalities of states reopening amid the COVID-19 pandemic. They also consider which party is ahead in the race for the Senate.  2894 no  What The 14.7% Unemployment Rate Means Former Commissioner of the Bureau of Labor Statistics Erica Groshen joins the podcast to discuss the latest jobs report, which showed a record unemployment level. Fri, 08 May 2020 20:50:00 -0000 What The 14.7% Unemployment Rate Means full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Former Commissioner of the Bureau of Labor Statistics Erica Groshen joins the podcast to discuss the latest jobs report, which showed a record unemployment level. Former Commissioner of the Bureau of Labor Statistics Erica Groshen joins the podcast to discuss the latest jobs report, which showed a record unemployment level.  1946 no  Biden Responds To Sexual Assault Allegation The team discusses the politics of Tara Reade's accusations of sexual assault against Biden and Biden's denial. They also weigh the impact of a Justin Amash run for president. Mon, 04 May 2020 21:41:00 -0000 Biden Responds To Sexual Assault Allegation full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The team discusses the politics of Tara Reade's accusations of sexual assault against Biden and Biden's denial. They also weigh the impact of a Justin Amash run for president. The team discusses the politics of Tara Reade's accusations of sexual assault against Biden and Biden's denial. They also weigh the impact of a Justin Amash run for president.  3612 no  The U.S. Is Starting To Reopen. Is It Ready? States around the country are beginning to reopen. Professor Crystal Watson of the Johns Hopkins School of Public Health discusses the systems they should have in place. Thu, 30 Apr 2020 21:30:00 -0000 The U.S. Is Starting To Reopen. Is It Ready? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver States around the country are beginning to reopen. Professor Crystal Watson of the Johns Hopkins School of Public Health discusses the systems they should have in place. States around the country are beginning to reopen. Professor Crystal Watson of the Johns Hopkins School of Public Health discusses the systems they should have in place.  2184 no  Is COVID-19 Already Hurting Trump Politically? The crew analyzes recent data showing Trump losing ground in swing states. They also ask how much reactions to the pandemic have been based on partisanship. Mon, 27 Apr 2020 21:59:00 -0000 Is COVID-19 Already Hurting Trump Politically? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew analyzes recent data showing Trump losing ground in swing states. They also ask how much reactions to the pandemic have been based on partisanship. The crew analyzes recent data showing Trump losing ground in swing states. They also ask how much reactions to the pandemic have been based on partisanship.  3332 no  Model Talk: Forecasting The Toll Of COVID-19 Dr. Chris Murray, creator of the frequently cited IHME COVID-19 model, joins a special edition of Model Talk. Wed, 22 Apr 2020 19:23:00 -0000 Model Talk: Forecasting The Toll Of COVID-19 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Dr. Chris Murray, creator of the frequently cited IHME COVID-19 model, joins a special edition of Model Talk. Dr. Chris Murray, creator of the frequently cited IHME COVID-19 model, joins a special edition of Model Talk.  2541 no  What Is Motivating The COVID-19 Protests? The crew discusses why protests against COVID-19 mitigation measures have popped up around the country. They also weigh the pros and cons of Biden's potential VP picks. Mon, 20 Apr 2020 22:08:00 -0000 What Is Motivating The COVID-19 Protests? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses why protests against COVID-19 mitigation measures have popped up around the country. They also weigh the pros and cons of Biden's potential VP picks. The crew discusses why protests against COVID-19 mitigation measures have popped up around the country. They also weigh the pros and cons of Biden's potential VP picks.  3728 no  How To Hold An Election During A Crisis What has the United States done to ensure elections continue during past crises and what can the country do now to ensure this fall's election goes smoothly? Thu, 16 Apr 2020 19:30:00 -0000 How To Hold An Election During A Crisis full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver What has the United States done to ensure elections continue during past crises and what can the country do now to ensure this fall's election goes smoothly? What has the United States done to ensure elections continue during past crises and what can the country do now to ensure this fall's election goes smoothly?  3098 no  Our 2020 Election Priors Now that Democrats have settled on Joe Biden, the crew discusses their priors for the presidential general election. They also track where we are in the COVID-19 pandemic. Mon, 13 Apr 2020 21:14:00 -0000 Our 2020 Election Priors full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Now that Democrats have settled on Joe Biden, the crew discusses their priors for the presidential general election. They also track where we are in the COVID-19 pandemic. Now that Democrats have settled on Joe Biden, the crew discusses their priors for the presidential general election. They also track where we are in the COVID-19 pandemic.  3156 no  Emergency Podcast: Sanders Drops Out The crew reacts to Sen. Bernie Sanders's decision to suspend his campaign for president. Wed, 08 Apr 2020 20:46:00 -0000 Emergency Podcast: Sanders Drops Out full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to Sen. Bernie Sanders's decision to suspend his campaign for president. The crew reacts to Sen. Bernie Sanders's decision to suspend his campaign for president.  1856 no  Wisconsin's Election Is A Mess The crew digs into the challenges facing Wisconsin's election, given partisanship and the COVID-19 pandemic. They also take stock of where we are in the arc of the crisis. Mon, 06 Apr 2020 21:30:00 -0000 Wisconsin's Election Is A Mess full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew digs into the challenges facing Wisconsin's election, given partisanship and the COVID-19 pandemic. They also take stock of where we are in the arc of the crisis. The crew digs into the challenges facing Wisconsin's election, given partisanship and the COVID-19 pandemic. They also take stock of where we are in the arc of the crisis.  3189 no  Why It's So Hard To Forecast The Impact Of COVID-19 FiveThirtyEight's science writer Maggie Koerth and quantitative editor Laura Bronner join the podcast to discuss the challenges of modeling the impact of COVID-19. Thu, 02 Apr 2020 20:03:00 -0000 Why It's So Hard To Forecast The Impact Of COVID-19 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver FiveThirtyEight's science writer Maggie Koerth and quantitative editor Laura Bronner join the podcast to discuss the challenges of modeling the impact of COVID-19. FiveThirtyEight's science writer Maggie Koerth and quantitative editor Laura Bronner join the podcast to discuss the challenges of modeling the impact of COVID-19.  2022 no  Why Trump's Approval Rating Has Increased The crew discusses where we are in the arc of the COVID-19 crisis, how Americans are rating the president's performance, and the significance of the DPA. Mon, 30 Mar 2020 21:27:00 -0000 Why Trump's Approval Rating Has Increased full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses where we are in the arc of the COVID-19 crisis, how Americans are rating the president's performance, and the significance of the DPA. The crew discusses where we are in the arc of the COVID-19 crisis, how Americans are rating the president's performance, and the significance of the DPA.  3054 no  COVID-19 Broke The Jobless Claims Chart Economics reporter Ben Casselman joins Galen Druke and Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux to discuss the stunning unemployment claims numbers from last week. Thu, 26 Mar 2020 21:20:00 -0000 COVID-19 Broke The Jobless Claims Chart full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Economics reporter Ben Casselman joins Galen Druke and Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux to discuss the stunning unemployment claims numbers from last week. Economics reporter Ben Casselman joins Galen Druke and Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux to discuss the stunning unemployment claims numbers from last week.  2049 no  How COVID-19 Is -- And Isn't -- Changing Politics The crew discusses how the COVID-19 pandemic is affecting the politics of Washington, D.C. and how it's disrupting the 2020 presidential race. Mon, 23 Mar 2020 21:25:00 -0000 How COVID-19 Is -- And Isn't -- Changing Politics full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses how the COVID-19 pandemic is affecting the politics of Washington, D.C. and how it's disrupting the 2020 presidential race. The crew discusses how the COVID-19 pandemic is affecting the politics of Washington, D.C. and how it's disrupting the 2020 presidential race.  3111 no  How COVID-19 Is Changing The Economy Economist Tara Sinclair joins Galen Druke and Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux to discuss the economic impact of the COVID-19 pandemic so far. Fri, 20 Mar 2020 19:36:00 -0000 How COVID-19 Is Changing The Economy full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Economist Tara Sinclair joins Galen Druke and Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux to discuss the economic impact of the COVID-19 pandemic so far. Economist Tara Sinclair joins Galen Druke and Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux to discuss the economic impact of the COVID-19 pandemic so far.  2446 no  How COVID-19 Affected Tuesday's Vote FiveThirtyEight's Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux and Nathaniel Rakich discuss the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic on Tuesday night's primary elections. Wed, 18 Mar 2020 18:43:00 -0000 How COVID-19 Affected Tuesday's Vote full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver FiveThirtyEight's Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux and Nathaniel Rakich discuss the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic on Tuesday night's primary elections. FiveThirtyEight's Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux and Nathaniel Rakich discuss the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic on Tuesday night's primary elections.  1808 no  Coronavirus, Uncertainty, Politics The crew discusses the coronavirus crisis and the uncertainty and politics surrounding it. Mon, 16 Mar 2020 21:21:00 -0000 Coronavirus, Uncertainty, Politics full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the coronavirus crisis and the uncertainty and politics surrounding it. The crew discusses the coronavirus crisis and the uncertainty and politics surrounding it.  2961 no  Biden And Sanders Debate Amid Pandemic The crew reacts to the first Biden vs. Sanders one-on-one debate, which took place amid the coronavirus pandemic. Mon, 16 Mar 2020 03:46:00 -0000 Biden And Sanders Debate Amid Pandemic full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the first Biden vs. Sanders one-on-one debate, which took place amid the coronavirus pandemic. The crew reacts to the first Biden vs. Sanders one-on-one debate, which took place amid the coronavirus pandemic.  1120 no  The Democratic Primary Is No Longer Competitive The crew reacts to the latest round of Democratic primary results, in which Biden far outperformed Sanders. Wed, 11 Mar 2020 04:54:00 -0000 The Democratic Primary Is No Longer Competitive full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the latest round of Democratic primary results, in which Biden far outperformed Sanders. The crew reacts to the latest round of Democratic primary results, in which Biden far outperformed Sanders.  1916 no  Is Even Coronavirus Partisan? The crew discusses the results of a poll on coronavirus and previews the upcoming primary races. Mon, 09 Mar 2020 21:16:00 -0000 Is Even Coronavirus Partisan? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the results of a poll on coronavirus and previews the upcoming primary races. The crew discusses the results of a poll on coronavirus and previews the upcoming primary races.  2727 no  Model Talk: Biden Is A Clear Favorite Fri, 06 Mar 2020 21:38:00 -0000 Model Talk: Biden Is A Clear Favorite full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver 1795 no  Emergency Podcast: Warren Drops Out The crew reacts to the news that Sen. Elizabeth Warren is suspending her campaign for president. Thu, 05 Mar 2020 18:21:00 -0000 Emergency Podcast: Warren Drops Out full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the news that Sen. Elizabeth Warren is suspending her campaign for president. The crew reacts to the news that Sen. Elizabeth Warren is suspending her campaign for president.  1392 no  Biden Won Super Tuesday. What Now? The crew reacts to Joe Biden's very strong performance on Super Tuesday and asks what comes next. Wed, 04 Mar 2020 06:13:00 -0000 Biden Won Super Tuesday. What Now? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to Joe Biden's very strong performance on Super Tuesday and asks what comes next. The crew reacts to Joe Biden's very strong performance on Super Tuesday and asks what comes next.  1940 no  What's At Stake On Super Tuesday The crew previews the races that will be decided on Super Tuesday and debates the effect Buttigieg's dropout will have. Mon, 02 Mar 2020 22:12:00 -0000 What's At Stake On Super Tuesday full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew previews the races that will be decided on Super Tuesday and debates the effect Buttigieg's dropout will have. The crew previews the races that will be decided on Super Tuesday and debates the effect Buttigieg's dropout will have.  3328 no  Biden Wins Big In South Carolina The crew reacts to Biden's big win in South Carolina and discusses what comes next in what looks to be a two person race. Sun, 01 Mar 2020 04:24:00 -0000 Biden Wins Big In South Carolina full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to Biden's big win in South Carolina and discusses what comes next in what looks to be a two person race. The crew reacts to Biden's big win in South Carolina and discusses what comes next in what looks to be a two person race.  1608 no  How Rep. James Clyburn Settled On Endorsing Biden Rep. James Clyburn endorsed Joe Biden on Wednesday. Galen Druke sat down with Clyburn ahead of his endorsement to discuss Biden, South Carolina and the Democratic Party. Wed, 26 Feb 2020 14:40:00 -0000 How Rep. James Clyburn Settled On Endorsing Biden full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Rep. James Clyburn endorsed Joe Biden on Wednesday. Galen Druke sat down with Clyburn ahead of his endorsement to discuss Biden, South Carolina and the Democratic Party. Rep. James Clyburn endorsed Joe Biden on Wednesday. Galen Druke sat down with Clyburn ahead of his endorsement to discuss Biden, South Carolina and the Democratic Party.  2029 no  What Went Down In The South Carolina Debate The crew reacts to a messy Democratic debate in South Carolina. Wed, 26 Feb 2020 05:28:00 -0000 What Went Down In The South Carolina Debate full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to a messy Democratic debate in South Carolina. The crew reacts to a messy Democratic debate in South Carolina.  2411 no  Sanders Wins Big In Nevada Nate Silver and editor of the Nevada Independent, Jon Ralston, join the podcast from Las Vegas to discuss the results of the Nevada caucuses. Sun, 23 Feb 2020 22:14:00 -0000 Sanders Wins Big In Nevada full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Nate Silver and editor of the Nevada Independent, Jon Ralston, join the podcast from Las Vegas to discuss the results of the Nevada caucuses. Nate Silver and editor of the Nevada Independent, Jon Ralston, join the podcast from Las Vegas to discuss the results of the Nevada caucuses.  2205 no  Bloomberg Stumbles In Chaotic Debate In a late night edition of the podcast, the crew reacts to the Nevada Democratic primary debate. Thu, 20 Feb 2020 06:15:00 -0000 Bloomberg Stumbles In Chaotic Debate full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In a late night edition of the podcast, the crew reacts to the Nevada Democratic primary debate. In a late night edition of the podcast, the crew reacts to the Nevada Democratic primary debate.  2161 no  Can Bloomberg Win?! The crew discusses Michael Bloomberg's chances of winning the nomination. They also debate whether Bernie Sanders has a lock on the Nevada caucuses. Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:56:00 -0000 Can Bloomberg Win?! full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses Michael Bloomberg's chances of winning the nomination. They also debate whether Bernie Sanders has a lock on the Nevada caucuses. The crew discusses Michael Bloomberg's chances of winning the nomination. They also debate whether Bernie Sanders has a lock on the Nevada caucuses.  3165 no  Model Talk: The Chance Of Chaos Increases Nate Silver and Galen Druke discuss how the Democratic primary forecast has updated since the New Hampshire primary. Fri, 14 Feb 2020 20:23:00 -0000 Model Talk: The Chance Of Chaos Increases full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Nate Silver and Galen Druke discuss how the Democratic primary forecast has updated since the New Hampshire primary. Nate Silver and Galen Druke discuss how the Democratic primary forecast has updated since the New Hampshire primary.  1563 no  Bernie Sanders Wins New Hampshire The crew reacts to the results of the New Hampshire primary, including a Sanders win, a close second for Buttigieg and a surprise third place finish for Klobuchar. Wed, 12 Feb 2020 07:15:00 -0000 Bernie Sanders Wins New Hampshire full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the results of the New Hampshire primary, including a Sanders win, a close second for Buttigieg and a surprise third place finish for Klobuchar. The crew reacts to the results of the New Hampshire primary, including a Sanders win, a close second for Buttigieg and a surprise third place finish for Klobuchar.  1863 no  Live From Manchester: A New Hampshire Preview At a live show in Manchester, the crew previews the New Hampshire primary, debates the likelihood of a contested convention and plays a game! Mon, 10 Feb 2020 17:01:00 -0000 Live From Manchester: A New Hampshire Preview full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver At a live show in Manchester, the crew previews the New Hampshire primary, debates the likelihood of a contested convention and plays a game! At a live show in Manchester, the crew previews the New Hampshire primary, debates the likelihood of a contested convention and plays a game!  4191 no  Live From The New Hampshire Debate The crew reacts to the Democratic primary debate in New Hampshire, from the spin room. Sat, 08 Feb 2020 04:38:00 -0000 Live From The New Hampshire Debate full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the Democratic primary debate in New Hampshire, from the spin room. The crew reacts to the Democratic primary debate in New Hampshire, from the spin room.  1674 no  The Results In Iowa The crew discusses the results -- so far -- from the Iowa caucuses. They also check in on the race in New Hampshire and the vote to acquit President Trump. Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:25:00 -0000 The Results In Iowa full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the results -- so far -- from the Iowa caucuses. They also check in on the race in New Hampshire and the vote to acquit President Trump. The crew discusses the results -- so far -- from the Iowa caucuses. They also check in on the race in New Hampshire and the vote to acquit President Trump.  2834 no  Chaos In Iowa The crew discusses the lack of results in the Democratic Iowa caucuses. Tue, 04 Feb 2020 06:19:00 -0000 Chaos In Iowa full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the lack of results in the Democratic Iowa caucuses. The crew discusses the lack of results in the Democratic Iowa caucuses.  1498 no  Model Talk: What To Expect From The Iowa Caucuses Nate Silver and Galen Druke discuss the latest polling in the final day before the Iowa caucuses. Sun, 02 Feb 2020 21:28:00 -0000 Model Talk: What To Expect From The Iowa Caucuses full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Nate Silver and Galen Druke discuss the latest polling in the final day before the Iowa caucuses. Nate Silver and Galen Druke discuss the latest polling in the final day before the Iowa caucuses.  2332 no  Stacey Abrams Thinks She'll Be President By 2040 As part of our When Women Run series, Clare Malone sat down with Stacey Abrams, former candidate for governor of Georgia. Fri, 31 Jan 2020 05:17:00 -0000 Stacey Abrams Thinks She'll Be President By 2040 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver As part of our When Women Run series, Clare Malone sat down with Stacey Abrams, former candidate for governor of Georgia. As part of our When Women Run series, Clare Malone sat down with Stacey Abrams, former candidate for governor of Georgia.  2048 no  When Women Run To better understand what it's really like to run for office as a woman, we spoke to women from every state who have done it -- 97 women in all. These are their stories. Wed, 29 Jan 2020 18:32:00 -0000 When Women Run full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver To better understand what it's really like to run for office as a woman, we spoke to women from every state who have done it -- 97 women in all. These are their stories. To better understand what it's really like to run for office as a woman, we spoke to women from every state who have done it -- 97 women in all. These are their stories.  3518 no  The Sanders Surge The crew assesses Bernie Sanders's improvement in the polls a week before the Iowa caucuses. They also discuss reporting from John Bolton's new book. Mon, 27 Jan 2020 23:21:00 -0000 The Sanders Surge full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew assesses Bernie Sanders's improvement in the polls a week before the Iowa caucuses. They also discuss reporting from John Bolton's new book. The crew assesses Bernie Sanders's improvement in the polls a week before the Iowa caucuses. They also discuss reporting from John Bolton's new book.  3546 no  The Primaries Project: There's Gotta Be A Better System...Right? This is the third installment of our audio documentary series "The Primaries Project," looking at how our primary system came to be and its effect on American politics. Thu, 23 Jan 2020 13:23:00 -0000 The Primaries Project: There's Gotta Be A Better System...Right? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver This is the third installment of our audio documentary series "The Primaries Project," looking at how our primary system came to be and its effect on American politics. This is the third installment of our audio documentary series "The Primaries Project," looking at how our primary system came to be and its effect on American politics.  1955 no  How Senators Are Calculating Impeachment Politics FiveThirtyEight's Perry Bacon Jr. and Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux join Galen Druke to discuss the political considerations at play in President Trump's impeachment trial. Wed, 22 Jan 2020 21:02:00 -0000 How Senators Are Calculating Impeachment Politics full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver FiveThirtyEight's Perry Bacon Jr. and Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux join Galen Druke to discuss the political considerations at play in President Trump's impeachment trial. FiveThirtyEight's Perry Bacon Jr. and Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux join Galen Druke to discuss the political considerations at play in President Trump's impeachment trial.  1642 no  Live From DC: America's Favorite Sandwich In front of a live audience in DC, the crew debates the electoral cases of the leading Democratic candidates. The also discuss electability and guess what America thinks. Mon, 20 Jan 2020 19:53:00 -0000 Live From DC: America's Favorite Sandwich full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In front of a live audience in DC, the crew debates the electoral cases of the leading Democratic candidates. The also discuss electability and guess what America thinks. In front of a live audience in DC, the crew debates the electoral cases of the leading Democratic candidates. The also discuss electability and guess what America thinks.  4393 no  The Primaries Project: The Effects Of Reform This is the second installment of our audio documentary series "The Primaries Project," looking at how our primary system came to be and its effect on American politics. Thu, 16 Jan 2020 03:42:00 -0000 The Primaries Project: The Effects Of Reform full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver This is the second installment of our audio documentary series "The Primaries Project," looking at how our primary system came to be and its effect on American politics. This is the second installment of our audio documentary series "The Primaries Project," looking at how our primary system came to be and its effect on American politics.  2718 no  The Last Pre-Iowa Debate The crew reacts to the candidates' performances in the last Democratic primary debate before the Iowa caucuses. Wed, 15 Jan 2020 13:18:00 -0000 The Last Pre-Iowa Debate full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the candidates' performances in the last Democratic primary debate before the Iowa caucuses. The crew reacts to the candidates' performances in the last Democratic primary debate before the Iowa caucuses.  1927 no  A Four-Way Pileup In Iowa The crew discusses the latest polling in Iowa, showing a tight four-way race. They also talk about Booker's decision to dropout and Tom Steyer's polling in NV and SC. Mon, 13 Jan 2020 22:36:00 -0000 A Four-Way Pileup In Iowa full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the latest polling in Iowa, showing a tight four-way race. They also talk about Booker's decision to dropout and Tom Steyer's polling in NV and SC. The crew discusses the latest polling in Iowa, showing a tight four-way race. They also talk about Booker's decision to dropout and Tom Steyer's polling in NV and SC.  2545 no  Model Talk: The Primary Forecast Is Live FiveThirtyEight's 2020 Democratic primary forecast is live. In a new installment of "Model Talk" Nate Silver discusses what went into creating it. Fri, 10 Jan 2020 21:37:00 -0000 Model Talk: The Primary Forecast Is Live full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver FiveThirtyEight's 2020 Democratic primary forecast is live. In a new installment of "Model Talk" Nate Silver discusses what went into creating it. FiveThirtyEight's 2020 Democratic primary forecast is live. In a new installment of "Model Talk" Nate Silver discusses what went into creating it.  2324 no  The Primaries Project: How 1968 Changed Everything This is the first installment of our audio documentary series "The Primaries Project," looking at how our primary system came to be and its effect on American history. Thu, 09 Jan 2020 05:01:00 -0000 The Primaries Project: How 1968 Changed Everything full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver This is the first installment of our audio documentary series "The Primaries Project," looking at how our primary system came to be and its effect on American history. This is the first installment of our audio documentary series "The Primaries Project," looking at how our primary system came to be and its effect on American history.  2023 no  How The Iran Conflict Could Affect 2020 The team discusses the political implication's of President Trump's decision to kill Iran's Maj. Gen. Qassem Suleimani in a drone strike. Mon, 06 Jan 2020 22:22:00 -0000 How The Iran Conflict Could Affect 2020 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The team discusses the political implication's of President Trump's decision to kill Iran's Maj. Gen. Qassem Suleimani in a drone strike. The team discusses the political implication's of President Trump's decision to kill Iran's Maj. Gen. Qassem Suleimani in a drone strike.  2837 no  The Biggest Political Moments Of 2019 The podcast crew looks back at the biggest political moments of 2019 and looks ahead to the most pressing questions of 2020. Mon, 30 Dec 2019 15:05:00 -0000 The Biggest Political Moments Of 2019 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew looks back at the biggest political moments of 2019 and looks ahead to the most pressing questions of 2020. The podcast crew looks back at the biggest political moments of 2019 and looks ahead to the most pressing questions of 2020.  2994 no  Eggnog And Listener Questions In this holiday installment of the podcast, the crew drinks eggnog and answers questions from listeners. Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:20:00 -0000 Eggnog And Listener Questions full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In this holiday installment of the podcast, the crew drinks eggnog and answers questions from listeners. In this holiday installment of the podcast, the crew drinks eggnog and answers questions from listeners.  2834 no  The House Impeaches President Trump President Donald Trump became the third president in American history to be impeached on Thursday. The podcast team discusses how we got here and what comes next. Thu, 19 Dec 2019 03:58:00 -0000 The House Impeaches President Trump full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver President Donald Trump became the third president in American history to be impeached on Thursday. The podcast team discusses how we got here and what comes next. President Donald Trump became the third president in American history to be impeached on Thursday. The podcast team discusses how we got here and what comes next.  1776 no  Do Voters' Second Choices Matter? The crew previews what to expect from this week's likely impeachment vote and debate how much voters' second choices matter in the Democratic primary. Mon, 16 Dec 2019 22:43:00 -0000 Do Voters' Second Choices Matter? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew previews what to expect from this week's likely impeachment vote and debate how much voters' second choices matter in the Democratic primary. The crew previews what to expect from this week's likely impeachment vote and debate how much voters' second choices matter in the Democratic primary.  2936 no  Conservatives Win Big In The UK Election University of Cambridge political scientists Helen Thompson and David Runciman join the podcast to break down the results of the 2019 British general election. Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:50:00 -0000 Conservatives Win Big In The UK Election full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver University of Cambridge political scientists Helen Thompson and David Runciman join the podcast to break down the results of the 2019 British general election. University of Cambridge political scientists Helen Thompson and David Runciman join the podcast to break down the results of the 2019 British general election.  2730 no  The Primary According To The Early States The crew shares a preview of FiveThirtyEight's polling averages in the early states. They also discuss the path Trump's presidency is on. Mon, 09 Dec 2019 22:56:00 -0000 The Primary According To The Early States full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew shares a preview of FiveThirtyEight's polling averages in the early states. They also discuss the path Trump's presidency is on. The crew shares a preview of FiveThirtyEight's polling averages in the early states. They also discuss the path Trump's presidency is on.  3180 no  The Legal Experts And The Polls We review the House testimony from legal scholars on whether Trump committed an impeachable offense and check out the results of our polling collaboration with Ipsos. Wed, 04 Dec 2019 23:20:00 -0000 The Legal Experts And The Polls full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver We review the House testimony from legal scholars on whether Trump committed an impeachable offense and check out the results of our polling collaboration with Ipsos. We review the House testimony from legal scholars on whether Trump committed an impeachable offense and check out the results of our polling collaboration with Ipsos.  2540 no  Emergency Podcast: Harris Drops Out The crew reacts to Sen. Kamala Harris's decision to drop out of the Democratic primary. Tue, 03 Dec 2019 23:07:00 -0000 Emergency Podcast: Harris Drops Out full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to Sen. Kamala Harris's decision to drop out of the Democratic primary. The crew reacts to Sen. Kamala Harris's decision to drop out of the Democratic primary.  2424 no  Is The Party Deciding? The crew looks at which candidates are racking up endorsements and whether there's a meaningful trend in favor of Biden. They also take stock of Harris's troubles on the trail Mon, 02 Dec 2019 23:19:00 -0000 Is The Party Deciding? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew looks at which candidates are racking up endorsements and whether there's a meaningful trend in favor of Biden. They also take stock of Harris's troubles on the trail The crew looks at which candidates are racking up endorsements and whether there's a meaningful trend in favor of Biden. They also take stock of Harris's troubles on the trail  3278 no  A Very FiveThirtyEight Thanksgiving The crew discusses public opinion on impeachment and plays a Thanksgiving-inspired game. Mon, 25 Nov 2019 23:14:00 -0000 A Very FiveThirtyEight Thanksgiving full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses public opinion on impeachment and plays a Thanksgiving-inspired game. The crew discusses public opinion on impeachment and plays a Thanksgiving-inspired game.  3583 no  What Went Down In The 5th Democratic Debate In a late night podcast, the crew reacts to the fifth Democratic primary debate. Thu, 21 Nov 2019 06:44:00 -0000 What Went Down In The 5th Democratic Debate full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In a late night podcast, the crew reacts to the fifth Democratic primary debate. In a late night podcast, the crew reacts to the fifth Democratic primary debate.  1594 no  Impeachment Hearings Day 4: Sondland Testifies The crew reacts to U.S. Ambassador to the E.U. Gordon Sondland's testimony in the fourth day of public impeachment hearings. Wed, 20 Nov 2019 22:37:00 -0000 Impeachment Hearings Day 4: Sondland Testifies full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to U.S. Ambassador to the E.U. Gordon Sondland's testimony in the fourth day of public impeachment hearings. The crew reacts to U.S. Ambassador to the E.U. Gordon Sondland's testimony in the fourth day of public impeachment hearings.  1810 no  Impeachment Hearings Day 3: The Phone Call The crew discusses what went down during the third day of public impeachment hearings. Wed, 20 Nov 2019 01:57:00 -0000 Impeachment Hearings Day 3: The Phone Call full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses what went down during the third day of public impeachment hearings. The crew discusses what went down during the third day of public impeachment hearings.  1464 no  The Buttigieg Bump 2.0 The crew discusses the latest polling out of Iowa, showing a shakeup in the race there. They also ask why education levels are such a key factor in how people vote. Mon, 18 Nov 2019 22:49:00 -0000 The Buttigieg Bump 2.0 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the latest polling out of Iowa, showing a shakeup in the race there. They also ask why education levels are such a key factor in how people vote. The crew discusses the latest polling out of Iowa, showing a shakeup in the race there. They also ask why education levels are such a key factor in how people vote.  3147 no  Yovanovich Testifies, Trump Attacks The crew reacts to the second day of public impeachment hearings. Fri, 15 Nov 2019 22:43:00 -0000 Yovanovich Testifies, Trump Attacks full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the second day of public impeachment hearings. The crew reacts to the second day of public impeachment hearings.  1775 no  Public Impeachment Hearings Begin The crew reacts to the first of many public impeachment hearings on President Trump's attempt to pressure Ukraine to investigate a political rival. Wed, 13 Nov 2019 23:48:00 -0000 Public Impeachment Hearings Begin full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the first of many public impeachment hearings on President Trump's attempt to pressure Ukraine to investigate a political rival. The crew reacts to the first of many public impeachment hearings on President Trump's attempt to pressure Ukraine to investigate a political rival.  2268 no  The FiveThirtyNATE Podcast The New York Times's Nate Cohn joins the podcast to discuss battleground state polling, the Electoral College and the state of the Democratic primary. Mon, 11 Nov 2019 23:09:00 -0000 The FiveThirtyNATE Podcast full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The New York Times's Nate Cohn joins the podcast to discuss battleground state polling, the Electoral College and the state of the Democratic primary. The New York Times's Nate Cohn joins the podcast to discuss battleground state polling, the Electoral College and the state of the Democratic primary.  3870 no  What The 2019 Election Results Mean FiveThirtyEight election analysts Nathaniel Rakich and Geoffrey Skelley break down the results of the 2019 elections. Wed, 06 Nov 2019 21:42:00 -0000 What The 2019 Election Results Mean full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver FiveThirtyEight election analysts Nathaniel Rakich and Geoffrey Skelley break down the results of the 2019 elections. FiveThirtyEight election analysts Nathaniel Rakich and Geoffrey Skelley break down the results of the 2019 elections.  2331 no  Free-For-All In Iowa The crew previews the key elections on the ballot this Election Day and debates the role healthcare is playing in Sen. Elizabeth Warren's plateauing in national polls. Mon, 04 Nov 2019 22:57:00 -0000 Free-For-All In Iowa full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew previews the key elections on the ballot this Election Day and debates the role healthcare is playing in Sen. Elizabeth Warren's plateauing in national polls. The crew previews the key elections on the ballot this Election Day and debates the role healthcare is playing in Sen. Elizabeth Warren's plateauing in national polls.  3076 no  Exit Interview: Tim Ryan Rep. Tim Ryan exited the presidential race last week. We ask him to be candid about his experience in an "exit interview." Thu, 31 Oct 2019 14:12:00 -0000 Exit Interview: Tim Ryan full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Rep. Tim Ryan exited the presidential race last week. We ask him to be candid about his experience in an "exit interview." Rep. Tim Ryan exited the presidential race last week. We ask him to be candid about his experience in an "exit interview."  2194 no  What Should Republicans Do? The crew debates the savviest political strategy for Senate Republicans on the issue of impeachment. They also discuss the death of al-Baghdadi and disagreement in the polls. Mon, 28 Oct 2019 21:52:00 -0000 What Should Republicans Do? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew debates the savviest political strategy for Senate Republicans on the issue of impeachment. They also discuss the death of al-Baghdadi and disagreement in the polls. The crew debates the savviest political strategy for Senate Republicans on the issue of impeachment. They also discuss the death of al-Baghdadi and disagreement in the polls.  3678 no  The Taylor Testimony The crew discusses the significance of U.S. envoy to Ukraine William Taylor's testimony. He claimed Trump made military aid contingent on politically-motivated investigations. Wed, 23 Oct 2019 19:44:00 -0000 The Taylor Testimony full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the significance of U.S. envoy to Ukraine William Taylor's testimony. He claimed Trump made military aid contingent on politically-motivated investigations. The crew discusses the significance of U.S. envoy to Ukraine William Taylor's testimony. He claimed Trump made military aid contingent on politically-motivated investigations.  1429 no  Medicare For Fall The podcast crew discusses the politics of Medicare for All in the Democratic primary. They also look at the latest impeachment polling. Mon, 21 Oct 2019 21:08:00 -0000 Medicare For Fall full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew discusses the politics of Medicare for All in the Democratic primary. They also look at the latest impeachment polling. The podcast crew discusses the politics of Medicare for All in the Democratic primary. They also look at the latest impeachment polling.  3141 no  Warren In The Hot Seat The crew reacts to the fourth Democratic primary debate. Wed, 16 Oct 2019 05:32:00 -0000 Warren In The Hot Seat full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the fourth Democratic primary debate. The crew reacts to the fourth Democratic primary debate.  2304 no  What To Look For In The 4th Debate The crew discusses the latest impeachment polling and previews the fourth Democratic primary debate. Mon, 14 Oct 2019 21:38:00 -0000 What To Look For In The 4th Debate full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the latest impeachment polling and previews the fourth Democratic primary debate. The crew discusses the latest impeachment polling and previews the fourth Democratic primary debate.  3437 no  Impeachment 101 Law professor Kate Shaw joins the podcast to discuss the laws and history behind impeachment and how they apply to today. Thu, 10 Oct 2019 21:15:00 -0000 Impeachment 101 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Law professor Kate Shaw joins the podcast to discuss the laws and history behind impeachment and how they apply to today. Law professor Kate Shaw joins the podcast to discuss the laws and history behind impeachment and how they apply to today.  2526 no  Is Ukraine Getting Worse For Trump? The podcast crew reviews the latest news in the impeachment inquiry and discusses the two parties' strategies. They also ask if Joe Biden is the Democratic frontrunner. Mon, 07 Oct 2019 21:46:00 -0000 Is Ukraine Getting Worse For Trump? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew reviews the latest news in the impeachment inquiry and discusses the two parties' strategies. They also ask if Joe Biden is the Democratic frontrunner. The podcast crew reviews the latest news in the impeachment inquiry and discusses the two parties' strategies. They also ask if Joe Biden is the Democratic frontrunner.  3574 no  How TV's Evolution Explains Our Politics New York Times TV critic James Poniewozik joins the podcast to explain how changes in television over the past forty years have shaped American politics. Thu, 03 Oct 2019 13:05:00 -0000 How TV's Evolution Explains Our Politics full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver New York Times TV critic James Poniewozik joins the podcast to explain how changes in television over the past forty years have shaped American politics. New York Times TV critic James Poniewozik joins the podcast to explain how changes in television over the past forty years have shaped American politics.  2196 no  Impeachment Is Becoming More Popular The crew looks at how public opinion on impeaching President Trump has changed in the week since Speaker Pelosi announced a formal inquiry. Mon, 30 Sep 2019 20:23:00 -0000 Impeachment Is Becoming More Popular full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew looks at how public opinion on impeaching President Trump has changed in the week since Speaker Pelosi announced a formal inquiry. The crew looks at how public opinion on impeaching President Trump has changed in the week since Speaker Pelosi announced a formal inquiry.  3022 no  The Whistleblower's Complaint It's only been 48 hours since we last recorded, but a lot has happened. We discuss the release of Trump's Ukraine call summary, the whistleblower's complaint and more. Thu, 26 Sep 2019 20:36:00 -0000 The Whistleblower's Complaint full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver It's only been 48 hours since we last recorded, but a lot has happened. We discuss the release of Trump's Ukraine call summary, the whistleblower's complaint and more. It's only been 48 hours since we last recorded, but a lot has happened. We discuss the release of Trump's Ukraine call summary, the whistleblower's complaint and more.  2163 no  What An Impeachment Inquiry Might Mean The crew gathers to discuss Nancy Pelosi's decision to launch an impeachment inquiry against President Trump. How'd we get here, and what might come next? Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:35:00 -0000 What An Impeachment Inquiry Might Mean full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew gathers to discuss Nancy Pelosi's decision to launch an impeachment inquiry against President Trump. How'd we get here, and what might come next? The crew gathers to discuss Nancy Pelosi's decision to launch an impeachment inquiry against President Trump. How'd we get here, and what might come next?  1472 no  Are Democrats Ready To Impeach Trump? The crew discusses how the Ukraine story could change the impeachment conversation for Democrats. They also debate whether Elizabeth Warren is now the frontrunner in Iowa. Mon, 23 Sep 2019 22:59:00 -0000 Are Democrats Ready To Impeach Trump? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses how the Ukraine story could change the impeachment conversation for Democrats. They also debate whether Elizabeth Warren is now the frontrunner in Iowa. The crew discusses how the Ukraine story could change the impeachment conversation for Democrats. They also debate whether Elizabeth Warren is now the frontrunner in Iowa.  2935 no  We Ran Into Andrew Yang At The Airport Nate and Galen ran into Andrew Yang waiting for the same return flight from the debate in Houston last week. They asked if he'd record a podcast and he obliged. Thu, 19 Sep 2019 11:52:00 -0000 We Ran Into Andrew Yang At The Airport full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Nate and Galen ran into Andrew Yang waiting for the same return flight from the debate in Houston last week. They asked if he'd record a podcast and he obliged. Nate and Galen ran into Andrew Yang waiting for the same return flight from the debate in Houston last week. They asked if he'd record a podcast and he obliged.  1574 no  The State Of *Both* 2020 Primaries The crew discusses the latest post-debate polling and what the GOP primary is teaching us about Trump's electoral strengths and weaknesses. Mon, 16 Sep 2019 22:13:00 -0000 The State Of *Both* 2020 Primaries full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the latest post-debate polling and what the GOP primary is teaching us about Trump's electoral strengths and weaknesses. The crew discusses the latest post-debate polling and what the GOP primary is teaching us about Trump's electoral strengths and weaknesses.  3283 no  What Went Down In The Third Democratic Debate The crew reacts to the third Democratic primary debate from the spin room floor in Houston, Texas. Fri, 13 Sep 2019 06:27:00 -0000 What Went Down In The Third Democratic Debate full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the third Democratic primary debate from the spin room floor in Houston, Texas. The crew reacts to the third Democratic primary debate from the spin room floor in Houston, Texas.  2104 no  How To Own The Debate The crew discusses possible strategies for the candidates on stage in the Democratic primary debate on Thursday. Mon, 09 Sep 2019 22:15:00 -0000 How To Own The Debate full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses possible strategies for the candidates on stage in the Democratic primary debate on Thursday. The crew discusses possible strategies for the candidates on stage in the Democratic primary debate on Thursday.  3387 no  The Gerrymandering Fight Moves To The States A North Carolina court panel threw out the state's legislative maps as a partisan gerrymander this week. Nancy Martorano Miller and Dave Wasserman discuss the implications. Thu, 05 Sep 2019 23:45:00 -0000 The Gerrymandering Fight Moves To The States full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver A North Carolina court panel threw out the state's legislative maps as a partisan gerrymander this week. Nancy Martorano Miller and Dave Wasserman discuss the implications. A North Carolina court panel threw out the state's legislative maps as a partisan gerrymander this week. Nancy Martorano Miller and Dave Wasserman discuss the implications.  1606 no  And Then There Were Ten The crew discusses the dynamic of the third Democratic primary debate, in which ten candidates will face off on a single night. They also ask: good use or bad use of polling? Tue, 03 Sep 2019 21:41:00 -0000 And Then There Were Ten full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the dynamic of the third Democratic primary debate, in which ten candidates will face off on a single night. They also ask: good use or bad use of polling? The crew discusses the dynamic of the third Democratic primary debate, in which ten candidates will face off on a single night. They also ask: good use or bad use of polling?  2653 no  A Constitutional Crisis In Britain? Helen Thompson and David Runciman join the podcast to discuss Boris Johnson's suspension of parliament and the politics of Brexit. Thu, 29 Aug 2019 18:11:00 -0000 A Constitutional Crisis In Britain? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Helen Thompson and David Runciman join the podcast to discuss Boris Johnson's suspension of parliament and the politics of Brexit. Helen Thompson and David Runciman join the podcast to discuss Boris Johnson's suspension of parliament and the politics of Brexit.  2733 no  The Winnowing Begins The crew takes a look at who has dropped out of the Democratic primary and why. They also assess the political risk of a hypothetical downturn in the economy. Mon, 26 Aug 2019 21:23:00 -0000 The Winnowing Begins full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew takes a look at who has dropped out of the Democratic primary and why. They also assess the political risk of a hypothetical downturn in the economy. The crew takes a look at who has dropped out of the Democratic primary and why. They also assess the political risk of a hypothetical downturn in the economy.  2917 no  The 2019 Elections FiveThirtyEight elections analysts Nathaniel Rakich and Geoffrey Skelley join the podcast to discuss the races on the ballot in 2019 and the current national environment. Thu, 22 Aug 2019 15:04:00 -0000 The 2019 Elections full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver FiveThirtyEight elections analysts Nathaniel Rakich and Geoffrey Skelley join the podcast to discuss the races on the ballot in 2019 and the current national environment. FiveThirtyEight elections analysts Nathaniel Rakich and Geoffrey Skelley join the podcast to discuss the races on the ballot in 2019 and the current national environment.  1800 no  Elizabeth Warren's Comeback The crew discusses how Elizabeth Warren gained ground after polling fifth or sixth nationally a handful of months ago. They also ask what's changed since the El Paso shooting. Mon, 19 Aug 2019 21:39:00 -0000 Elizabeth Warren's Comeback full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses how Elizabeth Warren gained ground after polling fifth or sixth nationally a handful of months ago. They also ask what's changed since the El Paso shooting. The crew discusses how Elizabeth Warren gained ground after polling fifth or sixth nationally a handful of months ago. They also ask what's changed since the El Paso shooting.  3327 no  Trump's Trade War Puts His Biggest Asset At Risk International economist Mary Lovely joins the podcast to discuss the effects of President Trump's trade war with China. Thu, 15 Aug 2019 04:07:00 -0000 Trump's Trade War Puts His Biggest Asset At Risk full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver International economist Mary Lovely joins the podcast to discuss the effects of President Trump's trade war with China. International economist Mary Lovely joins the podcast to discuss the effects of President Trump's trade war with China.  2251 no  How Much Does Iowa Matter? Following a weekend during which the 2020 candidates flooded Iowa, the crew debates the significance of the first-in-the-nation caucus state. Mon, 12 Aug 2019 21:09:00 -0000 How Much Does Iowa Matter? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Following a weekend during which the 2020 candidates flooded Iowa, the crew debates the significance of the first-in-the-nation caucus state. Following a weekend during which the 2020 candidates flooded Iowa, the crew debates the significance of the first-in-the-nation caucus state.  3484 no  "The Best Pollster In Politics" Ann Selzer, who conducts the "Iowa Poll" and has an A+ rating in FiveThirtyEight's pollster rankings, talks about the challenges of polling Iowa in 2020. Thu, 08 Aug 2019 04:32:00 -0000 "The Best Pollster In Politics" full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Ann Selzer, who conducts the "Iowa Poll" and has an A+ rating in FiveThirtyEight's pollster rankings, talks about the challenges of polling Iowa in 2020. Ann Selzer, who conducts the "Iowa Poll" and has an A+ rating in FiveThirtyEight's pollster rankings, talks about the challenges of polling Iowa in 2020.  2054 no  Can Trump's Words Incite Violence? The podcast team discusses the weekend's mass shootings and the relationship between political rhetoric and violence. Mon, 05 Aug 2019 21:47:00 -0000 Can Trump's Words Incite Violence? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast team discusses the weekend's mass shootings and the relationship between political rhetoric and violence. The podcast team discusses the weekend's mass shootings and the relationship between political rhetoric and violence.  3194 no  Live From Detroit: The State Of The Race Post-Debates The crew discusses the debates and the state of the 2020 Democratic primary race in downtown Detroit. Fri, 02 Aug 2019 06:15:00 -0000 Live From Detroit: The State Of The Race Post-Debates full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the debates and the state of the 2020 Democratic primary race in downtown Detroit. The crew discusses the debates and the state of the 2020 Democratic primary race in downtown Detroit.  4297 no  Democrats Battle It Out The left and moderate flanks of the Democratic Party debated big ideas in the second primary debate. Nate and Galen react from downtown Detroit. Wed, 31 Jul 2019 06:01:00 -0000 Democrats Battle It Out full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The left and moderate flanks of the Democratic Party debated big ideas in the second primary debate. Nate and Galen react from downtown Detroit. The left and moderate flanks of the Democratic Party debated big ideas in the second primary debate. Nate and Galen react from downtown Detroit.  2057 no  Are Democrats Moving Too Far Left? The crew debates the risks for 2020 Democrats of taking unpopular positions on issues like healthcare and immigration. The also discuss Democrats' next steps on impeachment. Mon, 29 Jul 2019 21:47:00 -0000 Are Democrats Moving Too Far Left? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew debates the risks for 2020 Democrats of taking unpopular positions on issues like healthcare and immigration. The also discuss Democrats' next steps on impeachment. The crew debates the risks for 2020 Democrats of taking unpopular positions on issues like healthcare and immigration. The also discuss Democrats' next steps on impeachment.  3242 no  Mueller Talks After months of back-and-forth with Democrats, former special counsel Robert Mueller testified before the U.S. House Judiciary and Intelligence committees on Wednesday. Wed, 24 Jul 2019 22:48:00 -0000 Mueller Talks full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver After months of back-and-forth with Democrats, former special counsel Robert Mueller testified before the U.S. House Judiciary and Intelligence committees on Wednesday. After months of back-and-forth with Democrats, former special counsel Robert Mueller testified before the U.S. House Judiciary and Intelligence committees on Wednesday.  2203 no  Racial Resentment As A Political Strategy The podcast crew discusses the role that racial resentment played in the 2016 and 2018 elections and debates whether Trump could use it to his advantage in 2020. Mon, 22 Jul 2019 21:57:00 -0000 Racial Resentment As A Political Strategy full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew discusses the role that racial resentment played in the 2016 and 2018 elections and debates whether Trump could use it to his advantage in 2020. The podcast crew discusses the role that racial resentment played in the 2016 and 2018 elections and debates whether Trump could use it to his advantage in 2020.  3537 no  Who's Going To Win Pennsylvania In 2020? The podcast heads to Pennsylvania to discuss the state's political trends and what they mean for 2020. Thu, 18 Jul 2019 21:21:00 -0000 Who's Going To Win Pennsylvania In 2020? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast heads to Pennsylvania to discuss the state's political trends and what they mean for 2020. The podcast heads to Pennsylvania to discuss the state's political trends and what they mean for 2020.  2313 no  Trump's Racist Tweets The podcast team discusses Trump's tweets appearing to target a group of congresswomen of color. They also debate the odds of a Democrat winning a Senate seat in Kentucky. Mon, 15 Jul 2019 22:04:00 -0000 Trump's Racist Tweets full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast team discusses Trump's tweets appearing to target a group of congresswomen of color. They also debate the odds of a Democrat winning a Senate seat in Kentucky. The podcast team discusses Trump's tweets appearing to target a group of congresswomen of color. They also debate the odds of a Democrat winning a Senate seat in Kentucky.  3263 no  Exit Interview: Eric Swalwell Rep. Eric Swalwell exited the presidential race this week. We ask him to be candid about his experience in an "exit interview." Thu, 11 Jul 2019 22:08:00 -0000 Exit Interview: Eric Swalwell full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Rep. Eric Swalwell exited the presidential race this week. We ask him to be candid about his experience in an "exit interview." Rep. Eric Swalwell exited the presidential race this week. We ask him to be candid about his experience in an "exit interview."  2123 no  Is Biden Still The Front-Runner? The podcast crew debates whether Joe Biden is still the front-runner in the Democratic primary race. They also discuss Rep. Justin Amash's decision to leave the GOP. Mon, 08 Jul 2019 21:42:00 -0000 Is Biden Still The Front-Runner? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew debates whether Joe Biden is still the front-runner in the Democratic primary race. They also discuss Rep. Justin Amash's decision to leave the GOP. The podcast crew debates whether Joe Biden is still the front-runner in the Democratic primary race. They also discuss Rep. Justin Amash's decision to leave the GOP.  2872 no  The Verdict On The Debates The podcast crew digs into data about how voters reacted to the first debates. They also discuss the new sexual assault accusation against President Trump. Mon, 01 Jul 2019 22:15:00 -0000 The Verdict On The Debates full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew digs into data about how voters reacted to the first debates. They also discuss the new sexual assault accusation against President Trump. The podcast crew digs into data about how voters reacted to the first debates. They also discuss the new sexual assault accusation against President Trump.  3722 no  Harris Wins Narrative. We'll See About The Voters. The crew reacts to night two of the first Democratic primary debates. Fri, 28 Jun 2019 06:11:00 -0000 Harris Wins Narrative. We'll See About The Voters. full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to night two of the first Democratic primary debates. The crew reacts to night two of the first Democratic primary debates.  2246 no  What Went Down At The First Democratic Debate The podcast team reacts to night one of the first Democratic primary debates. Thu, 27 Jun 2019 05:45:00 -0000 What Went Down At The First Democratic Debate full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast team reacts to night one of the first Democratic primary debates. The podcast team reacts to night one of the first Democratic primary debates.  2142 no  Lanes Emerge In The Democratic Primary The crew re-assesses the significance of "lanes" in the Democratic primary and looks at Trump's Iran strategy. Mon, 24 Jun 2019 21:53:00 -0000 Lanes Emerge In The Democratic Primary full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew re-assesses the significance of "lanes" in the Democratic primary and looks at Trump's Iran strategy. The crew re-assesses the significance of "lanes" in the Democratic primary and looks at Trump's Iran strategy.  3077 no  What's At Stake In The Final Week Of SCOTUS Decisions Legal reporter Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins the podcast to discuss key decisions the Supreme Court has made so far, and what is at stake in the final 12 cases. Fri, 21 Jun 2019 20:04:00 -0000 What's At Stake In The Final Week Of SCOTUS Decisions full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Legal reporter Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins the podcast to discuss key decisions the Supreme Court has made so far, and what is at stake in the final 12 cases. Legal reporter Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins the podcast to discuss key decisions the Supreme Court has made so far, and what is at stake in the final 12 cases.  2297 no  Who Is Persuadable In 2020? As Trump kicks off his reelection campaign, the crew debates who is persuadable in 2020. They also discuss the Democratic primary debate lineups. Mon, 17 Jun 2019 21:44:00 -0000 Who Is Persuadable In 2020? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver As Trump kicks off his reelection campaign, the crew debates who is persuadable in 2020. They also discuss the Democratic primary debate lineups. As Trump kicks off his reelection campaign, the crew debates who is persuadable in 2020. They also discuss the Democratic primary debate lineups.  3196 no  A Republican Strategist's Guide To 2020 Republican strategist and pollster Bill McInturff joins the podcast to discuss his report, "What Republicans Need to Know as We Move Toward the 2020 Election." Thu, 13 Jun 2019 20:05:00 -0000 A Republican Strategist's Guide To 2020 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Republican strategist and pollster Bill McInturff joins the podcast to discuss his report, "What Republicans Need to Know as We Move Toward the 2020 Election." Republican strategist and pollster Bill McInturff joins the podcast to discuss his report, "What Republicans Need to Know as We Move Toward the 2020 Election."  2684 no  Is Elizabeth Warren Surging? The crew examines whether the popular narrative of Elizabeth Warren's breakthrough is reflected in the data. They also discuss why Joe Biden backtracked on the Hyde Amendment. Mon, 10 Jun 2019 21:11:00 -0000 Is Elizabeth Warren Surging? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew examines whether the popular narrative of Elizabeth Warren's breakthrough is reflected in the data. They also discuss why Joe Biden backtracked on the Hyde Amendment. The crew examines whether the popular narrative of Elizabeth Warren's breakthrough is reflected in the data. They also discuss why Joe Biden backtracked on the Hyde Amendment.  3103 no  The D.C. Statehood Episode Representative Eleanor Holmes Norton and Majority Leader Steny Hoyer join the podcast to discuss Democrats' efforts to make D.C. the nation's 51st state. Thu, 06 Jun 2019 16:13:00 -0000 The D.C. Statehood Episode full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Representative Eleanor Holmes Norton and Majority Leader Steny Hoyer join the podcast to discuss Democrats' efforts to make D.C. the nation's 51st state. Representative Eleanor Holmes Norton and Majority Leader Steny Hoyer join the podcast to discuss Democrats' efforts to make D.C. the nation's 51st state.  2354 no  Are Voters Sexist? The crew discusses what we know about how voters respond to female candidates and how the women running for president in 2020 are navigating questions about their identity. Mon, 03 Jun 2019 21:30:00 -0000 Are Voters Sexist? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses what we know about how voters respond to female candidates and how the women running for president in 2020 are navigating questions about their identity. The crew discusses what we know about how voters respond to female candidates and how the women running for president in 2020 are navigating questions about their identity.  3195 no  Are Nationalist Victories Around The World Connected? University of Cambridge professors Helen Thompson and David Runciman join the podcast to discuss what appear to be a string of similar outcomes in elections around the world. Fri, 31 May 2019 18:54:00 -0000 Are Nationalist Victories Around The World Connected? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver University of Cambridge professors Helen Thompson and David Runciman join the podcast to discuss what appear to be a string of similar outcomes in elections around the world. University of Cambridge professors Helen Thompson and David Runciman join the podcast to discuss what appear to be a string of similar outcomes in elections around the world.  2016 no  Is Pelosi's Trump Strategy Working? The crew discusses whether last week's back-and-forth between Pelosi and Trump achieved its reported goal. They also look at head-to-head polling in the Democratic primary. Tue, 28 May 2019 21:14:00 -0000 Is Pelosi's Trump Strategy Working? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses whether last week's back-and-forth between Pelosi and Trump achieved its reported goal. They also look at head-to-head polling in the Democratic primary. The crew discusses whether last week's back-and-forth between Pelosi and Trump achieved its reported goal. They also look at head-to-head polling in the Democratic primary.  2448 no  What We Can Learn From Tracking Trump's Falsehoods The Washington Post has been tracking every false or misleading claim Trump has made while in office. In this episode, we dig into the database. Thu, 23 May 2019 14:52:00 -0000 What We Can Learn From Tracking Trump's Falsehoods full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The Washington Post has been tracking every false or misleading claim Trump has made while in office. In this episode, we dig into the database. The Washington Post has been tracking every false or misleading claim Trump has made while in office. In this episode, we dig into the database.  1818 no  Have Americans Changed Their Minds On Abortion? The politics team examines Bill de Blasio's theory of the case, the rationale behind seemingly conflicting numbers on abortion and ask if Democrats can win the Senate in 2020. Mon, 20 May 2019 21:23:00 -0000 Have Americans Changed Their Minds On Abortion? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The politics team examines Bill de Blasio's theory of the case, the rationale behind seemingly conflicting numbers on abortion and ask if Democrats can win the Senate in 2020. The politics team examines Bill de Blasio's theory of the case, the rationale behind seemingly conflicting numbers on abortion and ask if Democrats can win the Senate in 2020.  3553 no  Why Some States Are Passing New Abortion Restrictions Alabama Gov. Kay Ivey signed the most restrictive abortion law in recent U.S. history into law on Wednesday. It's part of a larger trend of changing state level abortion law. Thu, 16 May 2019 10:57:00 -0000 Why Some States Are Passing New Abortion Restrictions full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Alabama Gov. Kay Ivey signed the most restrictive abortion law in recent U.S. history into law on Wednesday. It's part of a larger trend of changing state level abortion law. Alabama Gov. Kay Ivey signed the most restrictive abortion law in recent U.S. history into law on Wednesday. It's part of a larger trend of changing state level abortion law.  1653 no  The Politics Of Impeaching Trump The crew debates the possible political repercussions for Democrats of moving to impeach Trump. They also look at how some on the left have tried to discredit a CNN poll. Mon, 13 May 2019 21:42:00 -0000 The Politics Of Impeaching Trump full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew debates the possible political repercussions for Democrats of moving to impeach Trump. They also look at how some on the left have tried to discredit a CNN poll. The crew debates the possible political repercussions for Democrats of moving to impeach Trump. They also look at how some on the left have tried to discredit a CNN poll.  2741 no  Live From Houston: What Happened To The Bush GOP? In a live taping from Houston, Texas, the crew discusses how and why the GOP has changed from the party of Bush to the party of Trump. They also play a 2020 primary draft. Thu, 09 May 2019 17:39:00 -0000 Live From Houston: What Happened To The Bush GOP? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In a live taping from Houston, Texas, the crew discusses how and why the GOP has changed from the party of Bush to the party of Trump. They also play a 2020 primary draft. In a live taping from Houston, Texas, the crew discusses how and why the GOP has changed from the party of Bush to the party of Trump. They also play a 2020 primary draft.  4414 no  Live From Austin: Will Texas Be A Battleground In 2020? The crew is in Austin, Texas, where they debate whether the Lone Star State will be a battleground in 2020. They also play a heated round of trivia. Tue, 07 May 2019 03:17:00 -0000 Live From Austin: Will Texas Be A Battleground In 2020? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew is in Austin, Texas, where they debate whether the Lone Star State will be a battleground in 2020. They also play a heated round of trivia. The crew is in Austin, Texas, where they debate whether the Lone Star State will be a battleground in 2020. They also play a heated round of trivia.  3358 no  Mueller's Letter To Barr Special Counsel Mueller wrote AG Barr a letter expressing concerns about how he'd characterized the report's findings to Congress. The podcast crew reacts. Wed, 01 May 2019 20:13:00 -0000 Mueller's Letter To Barr full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Special Counsel Mueller wrote AG Barr a letter expressing concerns about how he'd characterized the report's findings to Congress. The podcast crew reacts. Special Counsel Mueller wrote AG Barr a letter expressing concerns about how he'd characterized the report's findings to Congress. The podcast crew reacts.  1689 no  Peto Buttichar 2020 The crew discusses the Democratic Party's reaction to Joe Biden entering the presidential race. They also ask why Sanders and Warren don't have more crossover support. Mon, 29 Apr 2019 22:22:00 -0000 Peto Buttichar 2020 full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the Democratic Party's reaction to Joe Biden entering the presidential race. They also ask why Sanders and Warren don't have more crossover support. The crew discusses the Democratic Party's reaction to Joe Biden entering the presidential race. They also ask why Sanders and Warren don't have more crossover support.  2895 no  How Joe Biden Could Win Former Vice President Joe Biden announced his candidacy for president on Thursday. The crew discusses the reasons he could win the nomination or come up short. Thu, 25 Apr 2019 11:28:00 -0000 How Joe Biden Could Win full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Former Vice President Joe Biden announced his candidacy for president on Thursday. The crew discusses the reasons he could win the nomination or come up short. Former Vice President Joe Biden announced his candidacy for president on Thursday. The crew discusses the reasons he could win the nomination or come up short.  1993 no  We Have The Mueller Report. Now What? The crew discusses how the various players are positioning themselves now that the Mueller report is public. Plus, the Democratic primary field expanded again. Mon, 22 Apr 2019 21:46:00 -0000 We Have The Mueller Report. Now What? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses how the various players are positioning themselves now that the Mueller report is public. Plus, the Democratic primary field expanded again. The crew discusses how the various players are positioning themselves now that the Mueller report is public. Plus, the Democratic primary field expanded again.  3034 no  Emergency Podcast: The Mueller Report The podcast team reacts to the release of the redacted Mueller report. Thu, 18 Apr 2019 22:07:00 -0000 Emergency Podcast: The Mueller Report full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast team reacts to the release of the redacted Mueller report. The podcast team reacts to the release of the redacted Mueller report.  2698 no  The State Of The Democratic Primary As the first quarter of 2019 comes to a close, the crew gives an assessment of state of the 2020 Democratic primary. Mon, 15 Apr 2019 22:36:00 -0000 The State Of The Democratic Primary full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver As the first quarter of 2019 comes to a close, the crew gives an assessment of state of the 2020 Democratic primary. As the first quarter of 2019 comes to a close, the crew gives an assessment of state of the 2020 Democratic primary.  2858 no  How Good Are FiveThirtyEight Forecasts? Our "Model Talk" series returns briefly to discuss the performance of FiveThirtyEight's forecast models over the past decade. We crunched the numbers and the results are in! Thu, 11 Apr 2019 20:17:00 -0000 How Good Are FiveThirtyEight Forecasts? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Our "Model Talk" series returns briefly to discuss the performance of FiveThirtyEight's forecast models over the past decade. We crunched the numbers and the results are in! Our "Model Talk" series returns briefly to discuss the performance of FiveThirtyEight's forecast models over the past decade. We crunched the numbers and the results are in!  1844 no  Do Democrats Want An Outsider In 2020? The crew debates the appeal of a political outsider for Democrats in 2020. They also look at the class divide among white voters how that affects their political behavior. Mon, 08 Apr 2019 22:16:00 -0000 Do Democrats Want An Outsider In 2020? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew debates the appeal of a political outsider for Democrats in 2020. They also look at the class divide among white voters how that affects their political behavior. The crew debates the appeal of a political outsider for Democrats in 2020. They also look at the class divide among white voters how that affects their political behavior.  3287 no  The Electoral College Episode Julia Azari and Seth Masket join the podcast to discuss the arguments for and against the Electoral College and how likely it is to actually change. Thu, 04 Apr 2019 19:02:00 -0000 The Electoral College Episode full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Julia Azari and Seth Masket join the podcast to discuss the arguments for and against the Electoral College and how likely it is to actually change. Julia Azari and Seth Masket join the podcast to discuss the arguments for and against the Electoral College and how likely it is to actually change.  2480 no  What Will Biden Do? Joe Biden has been accused of inappropriately touching a former legislator at a campaign event. Will that change his calculus about whether to get in the race? Mon, 01 Apr 2019 21:20:00 -0000 What Will Biden Do? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Joe Biden has been accused of inappropriately touching a former legislator at a campaign event. Will that change his calculus about whether to get in the race? Joe Biden has been accused of inappropriately touching a former legislator at a campaign event. Will that change his calculus about whether to get in the race?  2634 no  Can Statistics Solve Gerrymandering? Mathematician Moon Duchin joins Nate Silver and Galen Druke to discuss a method for spotting partisan gerrymandering that the Supreme Court considered Tuesday. Thu, 28 Mar 2019 20:38:00 -0000 Can Statistics Solve Gerrymandering? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Mathematician Moon Duchin joins Nate Silver and Galen Druke to discuss a method for spotting partisan gerrymandering that the Supreme Court considered Tuesday. Mathematician Moon Duchin joins Nate Silver and Galen Druke to discuss a method for spotting partisan gerrymandering that the Supreme Court considered Tuesday.  3459 no  Life After The Mueller Report The crew reacts to the principal findings of the Mueller report, according to Attorney General Bill Barr. Mon, 25 Mar 2019 19:44:00 -0000 Life After The Mueller Report full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the principal findings of the Mueller report, according to Attorney General Bill Barr. The crew reacts to the principal findings of the Mueller report, according to Attorney General Bill Barr.  3004 no  Emergency Podcast: Mueller Has Filed His Report In this emergency podcast, Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins Galen Druke to discuss what comes next now that Special Counsel Mueller has filed his report. Fri, 22 Mar 2019 23:36:00 -0000 Emergency Podcast: Mueller Has Filed His Report full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In this emergency podcast, Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins Galen Druke to discuss what comes next now that Special Counsel Mueller has filed his report. In this emergency podcast, Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins Galen Druke to discuss what comes next now that Special Counsel Mueller has filed his report.  777 no  Live From NY: It's A 2020 Draft! In a live taping of the podcast, the crew competes in a draft of the 2020 primary candidates. They also play "Good Use of Polling or Bad Use of Polling?" Thu, 21 Mar 2019 21:15:00 -0000 Live From NY: It's A 2020 Draft! full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In a live taping of the podcast, the crew competes in a draft of the 2020 primary candidates. They also play "Good Use of Polling or Bad Use of Polling?" In a live taping of the podcast, the crew competes in a draft of the 2020 primary candidates. They also play "Good Use of Polling or Bad Use of Polling?"  3874 no  Ranking 2020 Rollouts The crew takes stock of which candidates have done the best job introducing themselves in the early months of the primary. Mon, 18 Mar 2019 22:15:00 -0000 Ranking 2020 Rollouts full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew takes stock of which candidates have done the best job introducing themselves in the early months of the primary. The crew takes stock of which candidates have done the best job introducing themselves in the early months of the primary.  2571 no  The Moment Of Truth For Brexit David Runciman and Helen Thompson from the British "Talking Politics" podcast discuss the week in Brexit and what comes next. Fri, 15 Mar 2019 16:57:00 -0000 The Moment Of Truth For Brexit full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver David Runciman and Helen Thompson from the British "Talking Politics" podcast discuss the week in Brexit and what comes next. David Runciman and Helen Thompson from the British "Talking Politics" podcast discuss the week in Brexit and what comes next.  2277 no  How Beto O'Rourke Could Win Former El Paso congressman Beto O'Rourke is running for president. The crew discusses how he could win -- or lose -- the Democratic primary. Thu, 14 Mar 2019 11:43:00 -0000 How Beto O'Rourke Could Win full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Former El Paso congressman Beto O'Rourke is running for president. The crew discusses how he could win -- or lose -- the Democratic primary. Former El Paso congressman Beto O'Rourke is running for president. The crew discusses how he could win -- or lose -- the Democratic primary.  2062 no  How Divided Are Democrats? The podcast crew analyzes the divisions within the Democratic Party and makes sense of why potential 2020 candidates like Sherrod Brown decided not to run. Mon, 11 Mar 2019 22:04:00 -0000 How Divided Are Democrats? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew analyzes the divisions within the Democratic Party and makes sense of why potential 2020 candidates like Sherrod Brown decided not to run. The podcast crew analyzes the divisions within the Democratic Party and makes sense of why potential 2020 candidates like Sherrod Brown decided not to run.  3064 no  Iowa And New Hampshire Can Go To Hell Iowa, New Hampshire, South Carolina and Nevada. Why do those four states vote first and does the lineup make sense? Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:10:00 -0000 Iowa And New Hampshire Can Go To Hell full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Iowa, New Hampshire, South Carolina and Nevada. Why do those four states vote first and does the lineup make sense? Iowa, New Hampshire, South Carolina and Nevada. Why do those four states vote first and does the lineup make sense?  1847 no  Should We Cancel The Electoral College? The podcast crew discusses the latest candidate announcements, whether party endorsements matter, and the merits of the Electoral College. Mon, 04 Mar 2019 23:24:00 -0000 Should We Cancel The Electoral College? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew discusses the latest candidate announcements, whether party endorsements matter, and the merits of the Electoral College. The podcast crew discusses the latest candidate announcements, whether party endorsements matter, and the merits of the Electoral College.  2995 no  What We Learned From Cohen's Testimony The podcast team reacts to a day of testimony from President Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen. Thu, 28 Feb 2019 01:21:00 -0000 What We Learned From Cohen's Testimony full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast team reacts to a day of testimony from President Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen. The podcast team reacts to a day of testimony from President Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen.  1811 no  Our Best (Or Worst) Show The podcast crew discusses absentee ballot fraud in North Carolina and the threat of a primary challenge to Trump. They also play a round of "Guess What Americans Think." Mon, 25 Feb 2019 23:10:00 -0000 Our Best (Or Worst) Show full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The podcast crew discusses absentee ballot fraud in North Carolina and the threat of a primary challenge to Trump. They also play a round of "Guess What Americans Think." The podcast crew discusses absentee ballot fraud in North Carolina and the threat of a primary challenge to Trump. They also play a round of "Guess What Americans Think."  2738 no  All The President's Investigations The word is that Mueller will wrap up his investigation next week. Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux shares an overview of the legal troubles that will continue to follow the president. Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:38:00 -0000 All The President's Investigations full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The word is that Mueller will wrap up his investigation next week. Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux shares an overview of the legal troubles that will continue to follow the president. The word is that Mueller will wrap up his investigation next week. Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux shares an overview of the legal troubles that will continue to follow the president.  1731 no  How Bernie Sanders Could Win Sen. Bernie Sanders is running for president. The team describes both his path to success and failure in the primary. They also follow up on Trump's emergency declaration. Tue, 19 Feb 2019 22:25:00 -0000 How Bernie Sanders Could Win full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Sen. Bernie Sanders is running for president. The team describes both his path to success and failure in the primary. They also follow up on Trump's emergency declaration. Sen. Bernie Sanders is running for president. The team describes both his path to success and failure in the primary. They also follow up on Trump's emergency declaration.  2823 no  National Emergency Podcast The crew reacts to the news that President Trump plans to declare a national emergency at the southern border. Vox's Dara Lind also joins to discuss the border security deal. Thu, 14 Feb 2019 23:09:00 -0000 National Emergency Podcast full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reacts to the news that President Trump plans to declare a national emergency at the southern border. Vox's Dara Lind also joins to discuss the border security deal. The crew reacts to the news that President Trump plans to declare a national emergency at the southern border. Vox's Dara Lind also joins to discuss the border security deal.  2730 no  How Amy Klobuchar Could Win The crew discusses the arguments for and against Sen. Amy Klobuchar winning the Democratic nomination. They also assess the politics of the Green New Deal. Mon, 11 Feb 2019 22:52:00 -0000 How Amy Klobuchar Could Win full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the arguments for and against Sen. Amy Klobuchar winning the Democratic nomination. They also assess the politics of the Green New Deal. The crew discusses the arguments for and against Sen. Amy Klobuchar winning the Democratic nomination. They also assess the politics of the Green New Deal.  2856 no  The Mess In Virginia Democratic politics in Virginia are in upheaval. The team reacts to the scandals facing each of the top three Democrats in the state -- the governor, lt. governor and AG. Thu, 07 Feb 2019 20:10:00 -0000 The Mess In Virginia full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Democratic politics in Virginia are in upheaval. The team reacts to the scandals facing each of the top three Democrats in the state -- the governor, lt. governor and AG. Democratic politics in Virginia are in upheaval. The team reacts to the scandals facing each of the top three Democrats in the state -- the governor, lt. governor and AG.  1758 no  The Politics Of Taxing The Rich Some Democrats are floating new taxes on the super rich. The crew discusses the politics of those proposals. They also assess Cory Booker's path to the nomination. Mon, 04 Feb 2019 22:57:00 -0000 The Politics Of Taxing The Rich full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Some Democrats are floating new taxes on the super rich. The crew discusses the politics of those proposals. They also assess Cory Booker's path to the nomination. Some Democrats are floating new taxes on the super rich. The crew discusses the politics of those proposals. They also assess Cory Booker's path to the nomination.  2204 no  The Perot Effect What effect do third party candidates have in a two party system? This is an audio documentary about Ross Perot and the 1992 election that originally aired in October 2016. Sat, 02 Feb 2019 14:26:00 -0000 The Perot Effect full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver What effect do third party candidates have in a two party system? This is an audio documentary about Ross Perot and the 1992 election that originally aired in October 2016. What effect do third party candidates have in a two party system? This is an audio documentary about Ross Perot and the 1992 election that originally aired in October 2016.  2415 no  Do Americans Want A Candidate Like Howard Schultz? In light of Howard Schultz's possible presidential run as a "centrist independent," the crew discusses the appetite for such a candidate among Americans. Thu, 31 Jan 2019 15:36:00 -0000 Do Americans Want A Candidate Like Howard Schultz? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In light of Howard Schultz's possible presidential run as a "centrist independent," the crew discusses the appetite for such a candidate among Americans. In light of Howard Schultz's possible presidential run as a "centrist independent," the crew discusses the appetite for such a candidate among Americans.  2035 no  Shutdown Lessons (And 2020 Announcements) The crew discusses the political repercussions of the government shutdown and considers two Democratic presidential contenders -- Pete Buttigieg and Tulsi Gabbard. Mon, 28 Jan 2019 23:18:00 -0000 Shutdown Lessons (And 2020 Announcements) full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the political repercussions of the government shutdown and considers two Democratic presidential contenders -- Pete Buttigieg and Tulsi Gabbard. The crew discusses the political repercussions of the government shutdown and considers two Democratic presidential contenders -- Pete Buttigieg and Tulsi Gabbard.  3145 no  What To Make Of Roger Stone's Indictment In this installment of Mueller Talk, Amelia Thomson-Deveaux discusses the implications of longtime Trump adviser Roger Stone's indictment. Fri, 25 Jan 2019 18:22:00 -0000 What To Make Of Roger Stone's Indictment full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In this installment of Mueller Talk, Amelia Thomson-Deveaux discusses the implications of longtime Trump adviser Roger Stone's indictment. In this installment of Mueller Talk, Amelia Thomson-Deveaux discusses the implications of longtime Trump adviser Roger Stone's indictment.  897 no  How Kamala Harris Could Win The crew analyzes what Harris's path to the nomination could look like. They also react to Mueller's statement on the Buzzfeed report and discuss the role of the young left. Tue, 22 Jan 2019 22:19:00 -0000 How Kamala Harris Could Win full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew analyzes what Harris's path to the nomination could look like. They also react to Mueller's statement on the Buzzfeed report and discuss the role of the young left. The crew analyzes what Harris's path to the nomination could look like. They also react to Mueller's statement on the Buzzfeed report and discuss the role of the young left.  3223 no  Emergency Podcast: The Suborn Identity In this emergency installment, the crew reacts to a Buzzfeed News report that President Trump directed his lawyer, Michael Cohen, to lie to Congress. Fri, 18 Jan 2019 19:08:00 -0000 Emergency Podcast: The Suborn Identity full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In this emergency installment, the crew reacts to a Buzzfeed News report that President Trump directed his lawyer, Michael Cohen, to lie to Congress. In this emergency installment, the crew reacts to a Buzzfeed News report that President Trump directed his lawyer, Michael Cohen, to lie to Congress.  1765 no  How Kirsten Gillibrand Could Win New York Senator Kirsten Gillibrand is the latest in the Democratic field to make official moves toward running for president. The crew discusses her case for the nomination. Note: At 17:40, Nate Silver's audio may be a bit unclear. He says, "It's not that logical because, number one, a lot of Democrats are concerned about senators who allegedly grope people." Wed, 16 Jan 2019 21:18:00 -0000 How Kirsten Gillibrand Could Win full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver New York Senator Kirsten Gillibrand is the latest in the Democratic field to make official moves toward running for president. The crew discusses her case for the nomination. Note: At 17:40, Nate Silver's audio may be a bit unclear. He says, "It's not t New York Senator Kirsten Gillibrand is the latest in the Democratic field to make official moves toward running for president. The crew discusses her case for the nomination. Note: At 17:40, Nate Silver's audio may be a bit unclear. He says, "It's not that logical because, number one, a lot of Democrats are concerned about senators who allegedly grope people."  2219 no  How Julian Castro Could Win The crew discusses what Julian Castro's path to the Democratic nomination could look like. They also lay out a rubric for evaluating candidate strengths and talk shutdown. Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:25:00 -0000 How Julian Castro Could Win full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses what Julian Castro's path to the Democratic nomination could look like. They also lay out a rubric for evaluating candidate strengths and talk shutdown. The crew discusses what Julian Castro's path to the Democratic nomination could look like. They also lay out a rubric for evaluating candidate strengths and talk shutdown.  2785 no  Will Trump Face A Primary Challenge? Is Trump in danger of a serious challenge for the Republican nomination in 2020? Perry Bacon Jr. and Julia Azari join the podcast to discuss. Thu, 10 Jan 2019 22:45:00 -0000 Will Trump Face A Primary Challenge? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Is Trump in danger of a serious challenge for the Republican nomination in 2020? Perry Bacon Jr. and Julia Azari join the podcast to discuss. Is Trump in danger of a serious challenge for the Republican nomination in 2020? Perry Bacon Jr. and Julia Azari join the podcast to discuss.  1772 no  How Elizabeth Warren Could Win The crew discusses the paths to Elizabeth Warren winning -- and losing -- the 2020 Democratic nomination. They also look at the political repercussions of the shutdown. Mon, 07 Jan 2019 22:32:00 -0000 How Elizabeth Warren Could Win full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew discusses the paths to Elizabeth Warren winning -- and losing -- the 2020 Democratic nomination. They also look at the political repercussions of the shutdown. The crew discusses the paths to Elizabeth Warren winning -- and losing -- the 2020 Democratic nomination. They also look at the political repercussions of the shutdown.  3289 no  The Gerrymandering Project: Arizona In 2018, more states decided to put independent commissions in charge of redistricting. Arizona serves as an example of some of the challenges those commissions can face. Mon, 31 Dec 2018 13:59:00 -0000 The Gerrymandering Project: Arizona full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In 2018, more states decided to put independent commissions in charge of redistricting. Arizona serves as an example of some of the challenges those commissions can face. In 2018, more states decided to put independent commissions in charge of redistricting. Arizona serves as an example of some of the challenges those commissions can face.  2308 no  Our 2018 Politics Awards The crew looks back on the year in politics and gives out made up awards. They also share resolutions for 2019. Mon, 24 Dec 2018 13:04:00 -0000 Our 2018 Politics Awards full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew looks back on the year in politics and gives out made up awards. They also share resolutions for 2019. The crew looks back on the year in politics and gives out made up awards. They also share resolutions for 2019.  3384 no  Emergency Podcast: Mattis Is Out, Shutdown Is On (?) In an emergency episode of the podcast, the crew discusses Defense Secretary Jim Mattis's departure and the looming government shutdown. Fri, 21 Dec 2018 19:07:00 -0000 Emergency Podcast: Mattis Is Out, Shutdown Is On (?) full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In an emergency episode of the podcast, the crew discusses Defense Secretary Jim Mattis's departure and the looming government shutdown. In an emergency episode of the podcast, the crew discusses Defense Secretary Jim Mattis's departure and the looming government shutdown.  1729 no  Should Democrats Play Dirty? Democrats backed off a plan that would gerrymander New Jersey, while Republicans went ahead with a power grab in Wisconsin. The crew discusses why the parties play differently Mon, 17 Dec 2018 21:49:00 -0000 Should Democrats Play Dirty? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Democrats backed off a plan that would gerrymander New Jersey, while Republicans went ahead with a power grab in Wisconsin. The crew discusses why the parties play differently Democrats backed off a plan that would gerrymander New Jersey, while Republicans went ahead with a power grab in Wisconsin. The crew discusses why the parties play differently  3044 no  The Brexit Episode Two political science professors from the University of Cambridge join the podcast to explain what happened in Britain this week and what comes next. Thu, 13 Dec 2018 21:01:00 -0000 The Brexit Episode full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Two political science professors from the University of Cambridge join the podcast to explain what happened in Britain this week and what comes next. Two political science professors from the University of Cambridge join the podcast to explain what happened in Britain this week and what comes next.  1698 no  Trump's Turbulent Week President Trump is continuing to face possible legal trouble over campaign finance violations, meanwhile the White House is in the middle of another staffing shakeup. Mon, 10 Dec 2018 21:45:00 -0000 Trump's Turbulent Week full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver President Trump is continuing to face possible legal trouble over campaign finance violations, meanwhile the White House is in the middle of another staffing shakeup. President Trump is continuing to face possible legal trouble over campaign finance violations, meanwhile the White House is in the middle of another staffing shakeup.  2521 no  Something Is Fishy In North Carolina The crew reflects on how politics have changed since President H. W. Bush's time in office. They also speak with Prof. Michael Bitzer about possible election fraud in NC-09. Mon, 03 Dec 2018 22:22:00 -0000 Something Is Fishy In North Carolina full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The crew reflects on how politics have changed since President H. W. Bush's time in office. They also speak with Prof. Michael Bitzer about possible election fraud in NC-09. The crew reflects on how politics have changed since President H. W. Bush's time in office. They also speak with Prof. Michael Bitzer about possible election fraud in NC-09.  3245 no  Emergency Podcast: Cohen Is Cooperating With Mueller In an emergency installment, the crew reacts to news that Michael Cohen pleaded guilty for lying to Congress about the details of a potential Trump project in Moscow. Thu, 29 Nov 2018 20:53:00 -0000 Emergency Podcast: Cohen Is Cooperating With Mueller full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In an emergency installment, the crew reacts to news that Michael Cohen pleaded guilty for lying to Congress about the details of a potential Trump project in Moscow. In an emergency installment, the crew reacts to news that Michael Cohen pleaded guilty for lying to Congress about the details of a potential Trump project in Moscow.  1308 no  This Is Mueller Talk! After months of silence, the Mueller investigation is making news again. Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins the podcast to make sense of a big week of revelations. Thu, 29 Nov 2018 13:45:00 -0000 This Is Mueller Talk! full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver After months of silence, the Mueller investigation is making news again. Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins the podcast to make sense of a big week of revelations. After months of silence, the Mueller investigation is making news again. Amelia Thomson-DeVeaux joins the podcast to make sense of a big week of revelations.  1811 no  Can A Democrat Win In Mississippi? The final Senate election of 2018 is scheduled for Tuesday in Mississippi. The crew discusses the fault lines at play of race, geography and class. Mon, 26 Nov 2018 22:13:00 -0000 Can A Democrat Win In Mississippi? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The final Senate election of 2018 is scheduled for Tuesday in Mississippi. The crew discusses the fault lines at play of race, geography and class. The final Senate election of 2018 is scheduled for Tuesday in Mississippi. The crew discusses the fault lines at play of race, geography and class.  3161 no  Will Pelosi Be Replaced? The Democrats have a majority in the House, now they need a Speaker. The crew discusses whether Nancy Pelosi will be re-elected and what the vote says about the party. Mon, 19 Nov 2018 22:03:00 -0000 Will Pelosi Be Replaced? full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The Democrats have a majority in the House, now they need a Speaker. The crew discusses whether Nancy Pelosi will be re-elected and what the vote says about the party. The Democrats have a majority in the House, now they need a Speaker. The crew discusses whether Nancy Pelosi will be re-elected and what the vote says about the party.  3280 no  How Our Model Did In this post-mortem episode of "Model Talk," Nate discusses how our forecasts did and how we can improve them going forward. Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:25:00 -0000 How Our Model Did full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver In this post-mortem episode of "Model Talk," Nate discusses how our forecasts did and how we can improve them going forward. In this post-mortem episode of "Model Talk," Nate discusses how our forecasts did and how we can improve them going forward.  2528 no  A Post-Midterms 2020 Draft... Live! Live from New York, the team ranks the politicians most likely to win the 2020 Democratic primary. They also debrief on the latest results from the midterms. Mon, 12 Nov 2018 20:37:00 -0000 A Post-Midterms 2020 Draft... Live! full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver Live from New York, the team ranks the politicians most likely to win the 2020 Democratic primary. They also debrief on the latest results from the midterms. Live from New York, the team ranks the politicians most likely to win the 2020 Democratic primary. They also debrief on the latest results from the midterms.  3130 no  Midterms Review The team looks at some the underlying data from the 2018 midterms to understand the trends at play. Thu, 08 Nov 2018 21:18:00 -0000 Midterms Review full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver The team looks at some the underlying data from the 2018 midterms to understand the trends at play. The team looks at some the underlying data from the 2018 midterms to understand the trends at play.  2088 no  Emergency Podcast: Sessions Is Out President Trump has fired Attorney General Jeff Sessions and is replacing him with someone who may curtain the Mueller investigation. The crew reacts. Wed, 07 Nov 2018 22:19:00 -0000 Emergency Podcast: Sessions Is Out full FiveThirtyEight, 538, ESPN, Nate Silver President Trump has fired Attorney General Jeff Sessions and is replacing him with someone who may curtain the Mueller investigation. The crew reacts. President Trump has fired Attorney General Jeff Sessions and is replacing him with someone who may curtain the Mueller investigation. The crew reacts.  1588 no 